Melisma, Tufts New Music Magazine UP243
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Melisma, Tufts New Music Magazine
2004 -- 2021
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Media Advocacy Board
UP243
0.5 Linear Feet
2 Web sites
This collection contains issues of Melisma, Tufts New Music Magazine, and web crawls documenting its web presence. The objective of this publication is to inform the students of Tufts University and other readers of the most relevant, interesting and original aspects of music and its culture - in all of the subjectivity inherent in criticism and investigation.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into two series: Melisma and Web crawls.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of Melisma, Tufts New Music Magazine, and web crawls documenting its web presence. The objective of this publication is to inform the students of Tufts University and other readers of the most relevant, interesting and original aspects of music and its culture - in all of the subjectivity inherent in criticism and investigation.
- Melisma, 2004 -- 2021; UP243.001; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of Melisma, Tufts New Music Magazine. The objective of this publication is to inform the students of Tufts University and other readers of the most relevant, interesting and original aspects of music and its culture - in all of the subjectivity inherent in criticism and investigation.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  This collection is open for research.
  - Melisma, 2004-12; UP243.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    Open for research.
    Tufts new music magazine.
    Volume, issue
    1, 1
  - Melisma, 2005-03; UP243.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
    1, 2
  - Melisma, Fall, 2005; UP243.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    2, 1
  - Melisma, Spring, 2006; UP243.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    2, 2
  - Melisma, Autumn, 2006; UP243.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    3, 1
  - Melisma, Spring, 2007; UP243.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
    3, 2
  - Melisma, Winter, 2008; UP243.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    4, 1
  - Melisma, Spring, 2009; UP243.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
    Volume
    5
  - Melisma, Fall, 2009; UP243.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
    6
  - Melisma, Spring, 2010; UP243.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
    7
  - Melisma, Spring, 2012; UP243.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
    9
  - Melisma, Spring, 2013; UP243.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
    10.1
  - Melisma, Winter, 2014; UP243.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
    11.0
  - Melisma, Summer, 2014; UP243.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
    12.0
  - Melisma, Winter, 2014; UP243.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
    13.0
  - Melisma, Spring, 2015; UP243.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
    14.0
  - Melisma, Summer, 2015; UP243.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
    Two copies.
  - Melisma, Spring, 2016; UP243.001.001.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Melisma, Summer, 2016; UP243.001.001.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Melisma, Winter 2017; UP243.000030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Melisma, Spring, 2017; UP243.001.001.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Melisma, Fall 2017; UP243.001.001.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Melisma, Spring 2018; UP243.000031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Melisma, Summer 2018; UP243.001.001.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Melisma, Spring 2019; UP243.000032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Melisma, Summer 2019; UP243.000033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Melisma, Fall 2019; UP243.000028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Melisma, Spring 2021; UP243.000029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Melisma, 2021 December; UP243.000034 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Web crawls, 2015 -- 2019; UP243.002; 2 Web sites
  Quarterly web crawls of the Melisma Magazine websites crawled by DCA, as part of the Student Organizations web collection, to document the presesence of Tufts University student organizations on the web.
  Other Finding Aids
  To see all of websites crawled as part of the Student Organizations web collection, please visit https://archive-it.org/collections/6387
  - Melisma Magazine, 2015 -- 2020; UP243.002.00001
    General
    Frequency: quarterly crawl.
  - Melisma Magazine, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UP243.002.00002